{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Hello",
          "answers": [
            "مرکشتم",
            "ظJڡاحادح",
            "ملاس"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "ملاس"
        },
        {
          "question": "Mother",
          "answers": [
            "ردار",
            "ردام",
            "ردٮ"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "ردام"
        },
        {
          "question": "Two",
          "answers": [
            "راهح",
            "هس",
            "ود"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "ود"
        },
        {
          "question": "Goodbye",
          "answers": [
            "هن",
            "ظJڡاحادح",
            "هلٮ"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "ظJڡاحادح"
        },
        {
          "question": "Brother",
          "answers": [
            "رتحد",
            "ردارٮ",
            "رهاوح"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "ردارٮ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Five",
          "answers": [
            "تJڡه",
            "شش",
            "جنٮ"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "جنٮ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Please",
          "answers": [
            "د<ٮشح",
            "اJڡطل",
            "مهاوحیم ترذعم"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "اJڡطل"
        },
        {
          "question": "Daughter",
          "answers": [
            "رهوش",
            "رتحد",
            "رسٮ"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "رتحد"
        },
        {
          "question": "Ten",
          "answers": [
            "هد",
            "هن",
            "تشه"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "هد"
        },
        {
          "question": "Yes",
          "answers": [
            "مرکشتم",
            "هلٮ",
            "هن"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "هلٮ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Son",
          "answers": [
            "رد",
            "رهوش",
            "رسٮ"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "رسٮ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Three",
          "answers": [
            "ود",
            "هس",
            "ک<ٮ"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "هس"
        },
        {
          "question": "I'm sorry",
          "answers": [
            "د<ٮشح",
            "ظJڡاحادح",
            "مهاوحیم ترذعم"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "مهاوحیم ترذعم"
        },
        {
          "question": "Uncle",
          "answers": [
            "ود ره",
            "كاكا",
            "امام"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "ود ره"
        },
        {
          "question": "Four",
          "answers": [
            "هس",
            "راهح",
            "ود"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "راهح"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Red",
          "answers": [
            "آتی",
            "سرخ",
            "سبز"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "سرخ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Monday",
          "answers": [
            "دوشنبه",
            "سه‌شنبه",
            "چهارشنبه"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "دوشنبه"
        },
        {
          "question": "January",
          "answers": [
            "فوریه",
            "مارچ",
            "جولای"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "جولای"
        },
        {
          "question": "Blue",
          "answers": [
            "آبی",
            "زرد",
            "سیاه"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "آبی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Wednesday",
          "answers": [
            "چهارشنبه",
            "پنجشنبه",
            "جمعه"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "چهارشنبه"
        },
        {
          "question": "April",
          "answers": [
            "آوریل",
            "جون",
            "جولای"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "آوریل"
        },
        {
          "question": "Green",
          "answers": [
            "سبز",
            "سیاه",
            "قهوه‌ای"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "سبز"
        },
        {
          "question": "Friday",
          "answers": [
            "جمعه",
            "یکشنبه",
            "شنبه"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "جمعه"
        },
        {
          "question": "October",
          "answers": [
            "نوامبر",
            "اکتبر",
            "سپتامبر"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "اکتبر"
        },
        {
          "question": "White",
          "answers": [
            "سفید",
            "کلایین",
            "ایشفن"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "سفید"
        },
        {
          "question": "Sunday",
          "answers": [
            "یکشنبه",
            "شنبه",
            "دوشنبه"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "یکشنبه"
        },
        {
          "question": "August",
          "answers": [
            "آگوست",
            "سپتامبر",
            "اکتبر"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "آگوست"
        },
        {
          "question": "Black",
          "answers": [
            "سیاه",
            "نارنجی",
            "زرد"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "سیاه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Thursday",
          "answers": [
            "پنج‌شنبه",
            "سه‌شنبه",
            "یکشنبه"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "پنج‌شنبه"
        },
        {
          "question": "June",
          "answers": [
            "جون",
            "جولای",
            "آگوست"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "جون"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Spring",
          "answers": [
            "تابستان",
            "بهار",
            "زمستان"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "بهار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bread",
          "answers": [
            "نان",
            "آب",
            "چای"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "نان"
        },
        {
          "question": "To eat",
          "answers": [
            "خوردن",
            "رفتن",
            "نوشیدن"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "خوردن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Summer",
          "answers": [
            "پاییز",
            "تابستان",
            "بهار"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "تابستان"
        },
        {
          "question": "Apple",
          "answers": [
            "سیب",
            "انگور",
            "انار"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "سیب"
        },
        {
          "question": "To drink",
          "answers": [
            "نوشیدن",
            "خوردن",
            "رفتن"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "نوشیدن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Winter",
          "answers": [
            "زمستان",
            "پاییز",
            "بهار"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "زمستان"
        },
        {
          "question": "Rice",
          "answers": [
            "برنج",
            "سالاد",
            "آب"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "برنج"
        },
        {
          "question": "To go",
          "answers": [
            "رفتن",
            "آمدن",
            "دیدن"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "رفتن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Autumn",
          "answers": [
            "زمستان",
            "پاییز",
            "تابستان"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "پاییز"
        },
        {
          "question": "Tea",
          "answers": [
            "چای",
            "آب",
            "شیر"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "چای"
        },
        {
          "question": "To come",
          "answers": [
            "آمدن",
            "رفتن",
            "دیدن"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "آمدن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Weather",
          "answers": [
            "هوا",
            "باران",
            "برف"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "هوا"
        },
        {
          "question": "Coffee",
          "answers": [
            "قهوه",
            "شیر",
            "گوشت"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "قهوه"
        },
        {
          "question": "To see",
          "answers": [
            "دیدن",
            "شنیدن",
            "صحبت کردن"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "دیدن"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Table",
          "answers": [
            "صندلی",
            "میز",
            "تختخواب"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "میز"
        },
        {
          "question": "Shirt",
          "answers": [
            "کت",
            "بوت",
            "پیراهن"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "پیراهن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Head",
          "answers": [
            "چشم",
            "دست",
            "سر"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "سر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Chair",
          "answers": [
            "تختخواب",
            "چوکی",
            "پنجره"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "چوکی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Pants",
          "answers": [
            "کت",
            "تنبان",
            "بوت"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "تنبان/شلوار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Eye",
          "answers": [
            "گوش",
            "چشم",
            "دهان"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "چشم"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bed",
          "answers": [
            "تختخواب",
            "میبل",
            "فرش"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "تختخواب"
        },
        {
          "question": "Dress",
          "answers": [
            "پیراهن",
            "دامن",
            "لباس"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "لباس"
        },
        {
          "question": "Ear",
          "answers": [
            "چشم",
            "دهان",
            "گوش"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "گوش"
        },
        {
          "question": "Window",
          "answers": [
            "حمام",
            "پنجره",
            "آشپزخانه"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "پنجره"
        },
        {
          "question": "Shoes",
          "answers": [
            "کت",
            "کفش",
            "ژاکت"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "کفش"
        },
        {
          "question": "Nose",
          "answers": [
            "دست",
            "پانو",
            "بینی"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "بینی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Lamp",
          "answers": [
            "چراغ",
            "فرش",
            "میبل"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "چراغ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Coat",
          "answers": [
            "شلوار",
            "کت",
            "کفش"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "کت"
        },
        {
          "question": "Mouth",
          "answers": [
            "چشم",
            "پانو",
            "دهان"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "دهان"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Doctor",
          "answers": [
            "داکتر",
            "معلم",
            "مهندس",
            "انجنیر"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "داکتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Math",
          "answers": [
            "علوم",
            "ریاضی",
            "تاریخ"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "ریاضی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Car",
          "answers": [
            "بس",
            "ماشین",
            "روچرخه"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "ماشین"
        },
        {
          "question": "Teacher",
          "answers": [
            "معلم",
            "پرستار",
            "پولیس"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "معلم"
        },
        {
          "question": "Science",
          "answers": [
            "تاریخ",
            "جغرافیا",
            "علوم"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "علوم"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bus",
          "answers": [
            "قطار",
            "بس",
            "هواپیما"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "بس"
        },
        {
          "question": "Engineer",
          "answers": [
            "وکیل",
            "مهندس",
            "انجنیر",
            "راننده"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "مهندس/انجنیر"
        },
        {
          "question": "History",
          "answers": [
            "هنر",
            "تاریخ",
            "زیست‌شناسی"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "تاریخ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Train",
          "answers": [
            "مترو",
            "ریا‌ل‌قطار",
            "قایق"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "ریال‌قطار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Nurse",
          "answers": [
            "پرستار",
            "کشاورز",
            "پولیس"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "پرستار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Geography",
          "answers": [
            "شیمی/کیمیا",
            "جغرافیا",
            "موسیقی"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "جغرافیا"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bicycle",
          "answers": [
            "ماشین",
            "دوچرخه",
            "هواپیما"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "دوچرخه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Police",
          "answers": [
            "پولیس",
            "آتش‌نشان",
            "وکیل"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "پولیس"
        },
        {
          "question": "Art",
          "answers": [
            "هنر",
            "ادبیات",
            "تاریخ"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "هنر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Airplane",
          "answers": [
            "کشتی",
            "هواپیما",
            "مترو"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "هواپیما"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Tree",
          "answers": ["گل", "درخت", "کوه"],
          "correctAnswer": "درخت"
        },
        {
          "question": "Dog",
          "answers": ["بشک", "ماهی", "سگ"],
          "correctAnswer": "سگ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Happy",
          "answers": ["غمگین", "خوشحال", "عصبانی"],
          "correctAnswer": "خوشحال"
        },
        {
          "question": "Flower",
          "answers": ["دریا", "گل", "رودخانه"],
          "correctAnswer": "گل"
        },
        {
          "question": "Cat",
          "answers": ["سگ", "پشک", "مرغ"],
          "correctAnswer": "پشک"
        },
        {
          "question": "Sad",
          "answers": ["خوشحال", "عصبانی", "غمگین"],
          "correctAnswer": "غمگین"
        },
        {
          "question": "Mountain",
          "answers": ["چمن", "کوه", "دریاچه"],
          "correctAnswer": "کوه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bird",
          "answers": ["فیل", "شیر", "پرنده"],
          "correctAnswer": "پرنده"
        },
        {
          "question": "Angry",
          "answers": ["عصبانی", "ترسیده", "هیجان‌زده"],
          "correctAnswer": "عصبانی"
        },
        {
          "question": "River",
          "answers": ["دریاچه", "رودخانه", "باران"],
          "correctAnswer": "رودخانه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Fish",
          "answers": ["گاو", "گوسفند", "ماهی"],
          "correctAnswer": "ماهی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Afraid",
          "answers": ["ترسیده", "هیجان‌زده", "بیمار"],
          "correctAnswer": "ترسیده"
        },
        {
          "question": "Sea",
          "answers": ["باران", "دریا", "باد"],
          "correctAnswer": "دریا"
        },
        {
          "question": "Lion",
          "answers": ["مرغ", "شیر", "اسب"],
          "correctAnswer": "شیر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Excited",
          "answers": ["هیجان‌زده", "خسته", "بیمار"],
          "correctAnswer": "هیجان‌زده"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Hour",
          "answers": ["دقیقه", "روز", "ساعت"],
          "correctAnswer": "ساعت"
        },
        {
          "question": "School",
          "answers": ["مکتب", "بانک", "بیمارستان"],
          "correctAnswer": "مکتب"
        },
        {
          "question": "Cook",
          "answers": ["پختن", "جوشاندن", "سرخ کردن"],
          "correctAnswer": "پختن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Minute",
          "answers": ["ساعت", "دقیقه", "هفته"],
          "correctAnswer": "دقیقه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Hospital",
          "answers": ["کتابخانه", "شفاخانه", "بانک"],
          "correctAnswer": "شفاخانه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bake",
          "answers": ["پختن (در فر/کوره)", "پوست کندن", "خرد کردن"],
          "correctAnswer": "پختن (در فر/کوره)"
        },
        {
          "question": "Day",
          "answers": ["روز", "سال", "ماه"],
          "correctAnswer": "روز"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bank",
          "answers": ["شفاخانه", "کتابخانه", "بانک"],
          "correctAnswer": "بانک"
        },
        {
          "question": "Boil",
          "answers": ["سرخ کردن", "جوشاندن", "مخلوط کردن"],
          "correctAnswer": "جوشاندن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Week",
          "answers": ["روز", "ماه", "هفته"],
          "correctAnswer": "هفته"
        },
        {
          "question": "Library",
          "answers": ["رستوران", "کتابخانه", "هوتل"],
          "correctAnswer": "کتابخانه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Fry",
          "answers": ["سرخ کردن", "پوست کندن", "خرد کردن"],
          "correctAnswer": "سرخ کردن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Year",
          "answers": ["ماه", "سال", "روز"],
          "correctAnswer": "سال"
        },
        {
          "question": "Store",
          "answers": ["پارک", "رستوران", "فروشگاه"],
          "correctAnswer": "فروشگاه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Grill",
          "answers": ["کباب کردن", "خرد کردن", "پوست کندن"],
          "correctAnswer": "کباب کردن"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Price",
          "answers": ["قیمت", "تخفیف", "فروش"],
          "correctAnswer": "قیمت"
        },
        {
          "question": "Doctor",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "دکتر", "بیمار"],
          "correctAnswer": "دکتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Sunny",
          "answers": ["باران", "آفتابی", "ابری"],
          "correctAnswer": "آفتابی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Discount",
          "answers": ["خرید", "قیمت", "تخفیف"],
          "correctAnswer": "تخفیف"
        },
        {
          "question": "Nurse",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "دکتر", "دارو"],
          "correctAnswer": "پرستار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Rainy",
          "answers": ["برف", "باران", "طوفان"],
          "correctAnswer": "باران"
        },
        {
          "question": "Sale",
          "answers": ["تخفیف", "فروش", "نقد"],
          "correctAnswer": "فروش"
        },
        {
          "question": "Medicine",
          "answers": ["درمان", "دارو", "جراحی"],
          "correctAnswer": "دارو"
        },
        {
          "question": "Cloudy",
          "answers": ["باد", "ابری", "مه‌آلود"],
          "correctAnswer": "ابری"
        },
        {
          "question": "Cash",
          "answers": ["نقد", "تخفیف", "خرید"],
          "correctAnswer": "نقد"
        },
        {
          "question": "Hospital",
          "answers": ["کلینیک", "شفاخانه", "داروخانه"],
          "correctAnswer": "بیمارستان"
        },
        {
          "question": "Windy",
          "answers": ["بادی", "مه‌آلود", "آفتابی"],
          "correctAnswer": "بادی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Receipt",
          "answers": ["رسید", "تخفیف", "فروش"],
          "correctAnswer": "رسید"
        },
        {
          "question": "Clinic",
          "answers": ["بیمارستان", "کلینیک", "داروخانه"],
          "correctAnswer": "کلینیک"
        },
        {
          "question": "Snowy",
          "answers": ["طوفان", "برف", "باران"],
          "correctAnswer": "برف"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Computer",
          "answers": ["انترنت", "كمبيوتر", "تلفن"],
          "correctAnswer": "كمبيوتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Football",
          "answers": ["فوتبال", "باسكتبال", "تينس"],
          "correctAnswer": "فوتبال"
        },
        {
          "question": "Song",
          "answers": ["أهنك", "موسيقي", "خواننده"],
          "correctAnswer": "أهنك"
        },
        {
          "question": "Internet",
          "answers": ["تلفن", "إيميل", "إنترنت"],
          "correctAnswer": "إنترنت"
        },
        {
          "question": "Basketball",
          "answers": ["تينس", "فوتبال", "باسكتبال"],
          "correctAnswer": "باسكتبال"
        },
        {
          "question": "Music",
          "answers": ["خواننده", "گروه موسيقي", "موسيقى"],
          "correctAnswer": "موسيقى"
        },
        {
          "question": "Phone",
          "answers": ["كمبيوتر", "تلفن", "كبورد"],
          "correctAnswer": "تلفن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Swimming",
          "answers": ["أب بازى/ شنا", "دویدن", "دوجرخه سواري"],
          "correctAnswer": "شنا/أب بازى"
        },
        {
          "question": "Singer",
          "answers": ["أهنك", "موسيقى", "خواننده"],
          "correctAnswer": "خواننده"
        },
        {
          "question": "Email",
          "answers": ["إيميل", "وسایت", "كبورد"],
          "correctAnswer": "إيميل"
        },
        {
          "question": "Running",
          "answers": ["دویدن", "شنا/أب بازى", "دوجرخه سواري"],
          "correctAnswer": "دویدن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Band",
          "answers": ["كونسرت", "أهنك", "گروه موسيقى"],
          "correctAnswer": "گروه موسيقى"
        },
        {
          "question": "Software",
          "answers": ["نرم‌افزار", "سخت‌افزار", "وسایت"],
          "correctAnswer": "نرم‌افزار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Gymnastics",
          "answers": ["جيمناستيك", "بوس", "دوجرخه سواري"],
          "correctAnswer": "جيمناستيك"
        },
        {
          "question": "Concert",
          "answers": ["كونسرت", "أهنك", "موسيقى"],
          "correctAnswer": "كونسرت"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Passport",
          "answers": ["بلیط/تکت", "گذرنامه/شناسنامه", "چمدان"],
          "correctAnswer": "گذرنامه/شناسنامه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Newspaper",
          "answers": ["مجله", "روزنامه", "تلویزیون"],
          "correctAnswer": "روزنامه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Painting",
          "answers": ["نقاشی", "مجسمه‌سازی", "طراحی"],
          "correctAnswer": "نقاشی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Ticket",
          "answers": ["نقشه", "بلیط/تکت", "گذرنامه"],
          "correctAnswer": "بلیط/تکت"
        },
        {
          "question": "Magazine",
          "answers": ["رادیو", "تلویزیون", "مجله"],
          "correctAnswer": "مجله"
        },
        {
          "question": "Sculpture",
          "answers": ["گالری", "مجسمه‌سازی", "موزیم/موزه"],
          "correctAnswer": "مجسمه‌سازی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Luggage",
          "answers": ["راهنما", "چمدان/کیس سفر", "سیاست/تور"],
          "correctAnswer": "چمدان/کیس سفر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Television",
          "answers": ["رادیو", "تلویزیون", "اینترنت"],
          "correctAnswer": "تلویزیون"
        },
        {
          "question": "Drawing",
          "answers": ["نقاشی", "طراحی", "گالری"],
          "correctAnswer": "طراحی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Map",
          "answers": ["مقصد", "نقشه", "راهنما"],
          "correctAnswer": "نقشه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Radio",
          "answers": ["اینترنت", "مجله", "رادیو"],
          "correctAnswer": "رادیو"
        },
        {
          "question": "Gallery",
          "answers": ["گالری", "یوم نقاشی", "فلم/مو"],
          "correctAnswer": "گالری"
        },
        {
          "question": "Guide",
          "answers": ["سفر", "سیاست/تور", "راهنما"],
          "correctAnswer": "راهنما"
        },
        {
          "question": "Internet",
          "answers": ["مجله", "روزنامه", "اینترنت"],
          "correctAnswer": "اینترنت"
        },
        {
          "question": "Museum",
          "answers": ["گالری", "موزیم", "نقاشی"],
          "correctAnswer": "موزیم"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Experiment",
          "answers": ["تحقیق", "آزمایش", "نظریه"],
          "correctAnswer": "آزمایش"
        },
        {
          "question": "Car",
          "answers": ["دوچرخه/باسیکل", "موتر", "هواپیما"],
          "correctAnswer": "موتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Office",
          "answers": ["دفتر", "میز کار", "چاپگر"],
          "correctAnswer": "دفتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Laboratory",
          "answers": ["داده", "آزمایشگاه", "مشاهده"],
          "correctAnswer": "آزمایشگاه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bus",
          "answers": ["ماشین", "مترو", "بس/اتوبوس"],
          "correctAnswer": "بس/اتوبوس"
        },
        {
          "question": "Desk",
          "answers": ["تلفن", "میز کار", "چاپگر"],
          "correctAnswer": "میز کار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Research",
          "answers": ["تحقیق", "تحلیل", "فرضیه"],
          "correctAnswer": "تحقیق"
        },
        {
          "question": "Train",
          "answers": ["هواپیما", "ریل/قطار", "قایق"],
          "correctAnswer": "قطار/ ریل"
        },
        {
          "question": "Computer",
          "answers": ["چاپگر", "تلفن", "کامپیوتر"],
          "correctAnswer": "کامپیوتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Scientist",
          "answers": ["داده", "دانشمند", "فرضیه"],
          "correctAnswer": "دانشمند"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bicycle",
          "answers": ["کشتی", "دوچرخه/باسیکل", "کامبون/موتر باری"],
          "correctAnswer": "دوچرخه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Telephone",
          "answers": ["چاپگر", "تلفن", "میز کار"],
          "correctAnswer": "تلفن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Theory",
          "answers": ["تحلیل", "نظریه", "داده"],
          "correctAnswer": "نظریه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Airplane",
          "answers": ["اتاق", "هواپیما", "مترو"],
          "correctAnswer": "هواپیما"
        },
        {
          "question": "Printer",
          "answers": ["میز کار", "چاپگر", "دفتر"],
          "correctAnswer": "چاپگر"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Hospital",
          "answers": ["دارو", "شفاخانه", "نسخه"],
          "correctAnswer": "شفاخانه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Money",
          "answers": ["بانک", "پول", "حساب"],
          "correctAnswer": "پول"
        },
        {
          "question": "School",
          "answers": ["مکتب", "شاگرد", "معلم"],
          "correctAnswer": "مکتب"
        },
        {
          "question": "Doctor",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "داکتر", "بیمار/مریض"],
          "correctAnswer": "داکتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bank",
          "answers": ["وام/قرض", "سود", "بانک"],
          "correctAnswer": "بانک"
        },
        {
          "question": "Student",
          "answers": ["مکتب", "دانش‌آموز", "معلم"],
          "correctAnswer": "دانش‌آموز"
        },
        {
          "question": "Nurse",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "نسخه", "دارو/دوا"],
          "correctAnswer": "پرستار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Account",
          "answers": ["حساب", "قرض/وام", "پس‌انداز"],
          "correctAnswer": "حساب"
        },
        {
          "question": "Teacher",
          "answers": ["معلم", "صنف", "درس"],
          "correctAnswer": "معلم"
        },
        {
          "question": "Patient",
          "answers": ["بیمار/مریض", "پرستار", "داکتر"],
          "correctAnswer": "بیمار/مریض"
        },
        {
          "question": "Loan",
          "answers": ["سود", "سرمایه‌گذاری", "قرض/وام"],
          "correctAnswer": "قرض/وام"
        },
        {
          "question": "Class",
          "answers": ["امتحان", "صنف", "نمره"],
          "correctAnswer": "صنف"
        },
        {
          "question": "Medicine",
          "answers": ["دارو/دوا", "جراحی", "درمان"],
          "correctAnswer": "دارو/دوا"
        },
        {
          "question": "Interest",
          "answers": ["بودجه", "هزینه", "سود"],
          "correctAnswer": "سود"
        },
        {
          "question": "Lesson",
          "answers": ["درس", "مکتب", "دانشگاه"],
          "correctAnswer": "درس"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Sunny",
          "answers": ["بارانی", "آفتابی", "ابری"],
          "correctAnswer": "آفتابی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Computer",
          "answers": ["اینترنت", "کامپیوتر", "تلفن"],
          "correctAnswer": "کامپیوتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Football",
          "answers": ["فوتبال", "بسکتبال", "تنیس"],
          "correctAnswer": "فوتبال"
        },
        {
          "question": "Rainy",
          "answers": ["برفی", "بارانی", "طوفانی"],
          "correctAnswer": "بارانی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Internet",
          "answers": ["تلفن", "ایمیل", "اینترنت"],
          "correctAnswer": "اینترنت"
        },
        {
          "question": "Basketball",
          "answers": ["تنیس", "فوتبال", "بسکتبال"],
          "correctAnswer": "بسکتبال"
        },
        {
          "question": "Cloudy",
          "answers": ["باد", "ابری", "مه‌آلود"],
          "correctAnswer": "ابری"
        },
        {
          "question": "Phone",
          "answers": ["کامپیوتر", "تلفن", "کیبورد"],
          "correctAnswer": "تلفن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Swimming",
          "answers": ["شنا/آب‌بازی", "دویدن", "دوچرخه‌سواری"],
          "correctAnswer": "شنا/آب‌بازی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Windy",
          "answers": ["بادی", "مه‌آلود", "آفتابی"],
          "correctAnswer": "بادی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Email",
          "answers": ["ایمیل", "وبسایت", "کیبورد"],
          "correctAnswer": "ایمیل"
        },
        {
          "question": "Running",
          "answers": ["دویدن", "آب‌بازی/شنا", "دوچرخه‌سواری"],
          "correctAnswer": "دویدن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Snowy",
          "answers": ["طوفانی", "برفی", "بارانی"],
          "correctAnswer": "برفی"
        },
        {
          "question": "Software",
          "answers": ["نرم‌افزار", "سخت‌افزار", "وبسایت"],
          "correctAnswer": "نرم‌افزار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Gymnastics",
          "answers": ["جیمناستیک", "بوکس", "پایسکل‌رانی/دوچرخه‌سواری"],
          "correctAnswer": "جیمناستیک"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Hospital",
          "answers": ["دارو", "شفاخانه", "نسخه"],
          "correctAnswer": "شفاخانه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Money",
          "answers": ["بانک", "پول", "حساب"],
          "correctAnswer": "پول"
        },
        {
          "question": "School",
          "answers": ["مکتب", "شاگرد", "معلم"],
          "correctAnswer": "مکتب"
        },
        {
          "question": "Doctor",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "داکتر", "بیمار/مریض"],
          "correctAnswer": "داکتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bank",
          "answers": ["وام/قرض", "سود", "بانک"],
          "correctAnswer": "بانک"
        },
        {
          "question": "Student",
          "answers": ["مکتب", "دانش‌آموز", "معلم"],
          "correctAnswer": "دانش‌آموز"
        },
        {
          "question": "Nurse",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "نسخه", "دارو/دوا"],
          "correctAnswer": "پرستار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Account",
          "answers": ["حساب", "قرض/وام", "پس‌انداز"],
          "correctAnswer": "حساب"
        },
        {
          "question": "Teacher",
          "answers": ["معلم", "صنف", "درس"],
          "correctAnswer": "معلم"
        },
        {
          "question": "Patient",
          "answers": ["بیمار/مریض", "پرستار", "داکتر"],
          "correctAnswer": "بیمار/مریض"
        },
        {
          "question": "Loan",
          "answers": ["سود", "سرمایه‌گذاری", "قرض/وام"],
          "correctAnswer": "قرض/وام"
        },
        {
          "question": "Class",
          "answers": ["امتحان", "صنف", "نمره"],
          "correctAnswer": "صنف"
        },
        {
          "question": "Medicine",
          "answers": ["دارو/دوا", "جراحی", "درمان"],
          "correctAnswer": "دارو/دوا"
        },
        {
          "question": "Interest",
          "answers": ["بودیجه", "هزینه", "سود"],
          "correctAnswer": "سود"
        },
        {
          "question": "Lesson",
          "answers": ["درس", "مکتب", "دانشگاه"],
          "correctAnswer": "درس"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Hospital",
          "answers": ["دارو", "شفاخانه", "نسخه"],
          "correctAnswer": "شفاخانه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Money",
          "answers": ["بانک", "پول", "حساب"],
          "correctAnswer": "پول"
        },
        {
          "question": "School",
          "answers": ["مکتب", "شاگرد", "معلم"],
          "correctAnswer": "مکتب"
        },
        {
          "question": "Doctor",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "داکتر", "بیمار/مریض"],
          "correctAnswer": "داکتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bank",
          "answers": ["وام/قرض", "سود", "بانک"],
          "correctAnswer": "بانک"
        },
        {
          "question": "Student",
          "answers": ["مکتب", "دانش‌آموز", "معلم"],
          "correctAnswer": "شاگرد/دانش‌آموز"
        },
        {
          "question": "Nurse",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "نسخه", "دارو/دوا"],
          "correctAnswer": "پرستار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Account",
          "answers": ["حساب", "قرض/وام", "پس‌انداز"],
          "correctAnswer": "حساب"
        },
        {
          "question": "Teacher",
          "answers": ["معلم", "صنف", "درس"],
          "correctAnswer": "معلم"
        },
        {
          "question": "Patient",
          "answers": ["بیمار/مریض", "پرستار", "داکتر"],
          "correctAnswer": "بیمار/مریض"
        },
        {
          "question": "Loan",
          "answers": ["سود", "سرمایه‌گذاری", "قرض/وام"],
          "correctAnswer": "قرض/وام"
        },
        {
          "question": "Class",
          "answers": ["امتحان", "صنف", "نمره"],
          "correctAnswer": "صنف"
        },
        {
          "question": "Medicine",
          "answers": ["دارو/دوا", "جراحی", "درمان"],
          "correctAnswer": "دارو/دوا"
        },
        {
          "question": "Interest",
          "answers": ["بودجه", "هزینه", "سود"],
          "correctAnswer": "سود"
        },
        {
          "question": "Lesson",
          "answers": ["درس", "مکتب", "دانشگاه"],
          "correctAnswer": "درس"
        }
      ]

    },
    {
      "quiz": [
        {
          "question": "Car",
          "answers": ["موٹر", "بس", "بائیکل"],
          "correctAnswer": "موٹر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Office",
          "answers": ["دفتر", "میز کار", "تلفن"],
          "correctAnswer": "دفتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Hospital",
          "answers": ["شفاخانہ", "دواء", "جراحی"],
          "correctAnswer": "شفاخانہ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bus",
          "answers": ["بس", "قطار", "کشتی"],
          "correctAnswer": "بس"
        },
        {
          "question": "Desk",
          "answers": ["چوکی", "میز کار", "تلفن"],
          "correctAnswer": "میز کار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Doctor",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "مریض/بیمار", "داکتر"],
          "correctAnswer": "داکتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Train",
          "answers": ["مترو", "قطار", "طیارہ"],
          "correctAnswer": "قطار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Computer",
          "answers": ["تلفن", "کامپیوتر", "دفتر"],
          "correctAnswer": "کامپیوتر"
        },
        {
          "question": "Nurse",
          "answers": ["پرستار", "دارو/دوا", "بیمار"],
          "correctAnswer": "پرستار"
        },
        {
          "question": "Bicycle",
          "answers": ["بائیکل/دوچرخہ", "طیارہ", "کشتی"],
          "correctAnswer": "بائیکل/دوچرخہ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Printer",
          "answers": ["دفتر", "مطبعه", "میز کار"],
          "correctAnswer": "مطبعه"
        },
        {
          "question": "Patient",
          "answers": ["داکتر", "بیمار/مریض", "پرستار"],
          "correctAnswer": "بیمار/مریض"
        },
        {
          "question": "Airplane",
          "answers": ["قایق", "طیارہ", "ماشین"],
          "correctAnswer": "طیارہ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Telephone",
          "answers": ["چوکی", "تلفن", "میز کار"],
          "correctAnswer": "تلفن"
        },
        {
          "question": "Medicine",
          "answers": ["درمان", "دارو/دوا", "نسخه"],
          "correctAnswer": "دارو/دوا"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
